Kostadis Roussos: Hello, Wade.
Wade Brown: I was wondering, like, it's 3 minutes and nobody's here!
Wade Brown: Where is everyone?
Wade Brown: Am I even here?
Wade Brown: Can you not hear me?
Wade Brown: Oh, dear, you can't…
Wade Brown: I see a finger.
Wade Brown: Hi, Wayne. Good evening.
Wade Brown: How it goes.
David Mendenhall: Mike told me he fixed a bug.
Wade Brown: That was last week, yeah.
Wade Brown: Nice. Or something like that, I don't know. I got nothing going on, I mean, I'm not billin' hours, so it's not costing you anything, just…
David Mendenhall: I know, I told Mike, he's got bugs, give them to you.
Wade Brown: Okay, that's fine. I mean, I…
Wade Brown: I am totally fine just being on retainer until you need me, like, it's totally cool by me.
David Mendenhall: That's very helpful. Thank you. Appreciate it.
Wade Brown: I tried to set that up with Caroline long, long, long ago. I was like, look, I don't want to just take all this knowledge and run, but, like, I also don't want to sit around and do stuff I don't want to do. So, like, can we find a middle ground? And they never did, so…
David Mendenhall: Well, hopefully this works well for you.
Wade Brown: Yeah, you can see the TV over there?
David Mendenhall: I see a box that says Roku.
Wade Brown: Well, that's just the… that's just the, panel, whatever.
Wade Brown: Yeah, because I don't really want to see the TV when I'm working unless I need to.
Wade Brown: Yeah, the timer had the wrong… or the…
Wade Brown: The USB tuner had the wrong clock on it, so it was just constantly jittering.
Wade Brown: Not too hard.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Hello, hello?
Wade Brown: Can you hear us now, Kostadis?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I can.
Wade Brown: Alright, are you drinking water?
Gary Young: about.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I'm drinking alcohol.
Wade Brown: Same thing.
Kostadis Roussos: Nope.
Kostadis Roussos: Wine is the nectar of the gods. Alcohol is something else.
Wade Brown: I had, I had some… some sort of, Greek concoction that was, like, Kahlua mixed with,
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, I can't hear you, hold on!
Wade Brown: The fuck, man!
David Mendenhall: Kostadis Kostadis, Kostadis, Kostadis, Kostadis.
Kostadis Roussos: Say it again?
Wade Brown: So I… when I was in, I think Santorini, I had some weird concoction that was, like, Kahlua mixed with, Jaeger. It's fantastic.
Kostadis Roussos: This is a mixed drink of some kind.
Wade Brown: This was a bottle, a single bottle.
Wade Brown: I might actually be able to find the name of it, because I… I sent it home to Nathan, I'm like, you gotta see if you can find this at home. I was like, well, we could just mix Kahlua and Jaeger.
Kostadis Roussos: 22?
Wade Brown: No.
David Mendenhall: Jaeger?
Wade Brown: I know, it sounds horrible.
David Mendenhall: They can do a lot better than that.
Wade Brown: Dude, I'm 12.
Wade Brown: Let's see…
David Mendenhall: Were you drinking Kahlua and Jaeger when you were 12?
Wade Brown: Anyway, I'm just saying I have kid taste buds.
David Mendenhall: Oh.
David Mendenhall: I actually didn't drink until I was 21.
Wade Brown: Oh… Really?
Gary Young: Me either.
Wade Brown: Me? Neither… no, I had very, very small amounts of alcohol before 21.
Kostadis Roussos: I was drunk for the first time when I was 4.
David Mendenhall: I had church wine.
Gary Young: I can believe that sucks.
David Mendenhall: When you were, what, 4?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: You're so Greek.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Wade Brown: Hell yeah.
Gary Young: Dave, how are you?
Kostadis Roussos: By the time I got to college, the whole idea of getting drunk did not appeal to me at all.
Kostadis Roussos: knowledge.
Gary Young: Maybe that's why you're a successful adult now.
Kostadis Roussos: Who knows? Who knows?
Kostadis Roussos: Or maybe, you know, it reflects the college wasted.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, I should add more fine college.
David Mendenhall: In retrospect.
Wade Brown: This was the staff SIG.
Wade Brown: Canava Santorini.
Wade Brown: Liquor, coffee, and anise.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, that's not… that's not Jaeger.
Wade Brown: Jaeger is Annis!
David Mendenhall: So is Absinthe.
Wade Brown: Yeah, in different quantity. This tastes much more like Jaeger than Absinthe.
Wade Brown: Anyway, this shit was fantastic.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you put it in the Discord chat?
Wade Brown: Oh, yeah.
Wade Brown: I mean, I don't know if it's for anybody who has taste buds that are, you know, beyond 16-year-old or whatever, but, you know.
Wade Brown: Le Queer Coffee Anise.
David Mendenhall: Oh.
David Mendenhall: Coffee? Oh, how funny.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: There you go.
Kostadis Roussos: It's Uzo with coffee and liquor.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Wade Brown: It was very good.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm just saying, and this means that Uza, they put… it's probably Uzzo, not Jaeger, but yes.
Wade Brown: I agree.
David Mendenhall: Look at that.
Wade Brown: I'm just letting you know what it tastes like.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, no, I know, but, like, the idea of Jaeger just, like…
Wade Brown: Oh, you're too proud for Jaeger.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I'm just surprised that a Greek…
Kostadis Roussos: concoctionists would use Jaeger, like, that actually costs more money than using Uzo, that's what I'm saying.
Wade Brown: Yeah, I would have bought it, except, like, oh, we can only ship back, like, 10 bottles at a time. Like, I'm not buying 10 bottles of this stuff.
David Mendenhall: Why are we in the forest?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, because I… I was… I needed to put you somewhere… never mind, you're not there.
Wade Brown: Alright, I should probably be logging in.
Kostadis Roussos: Because I was working on maps, and then I realized that you guys were about to log in, and I didn't want you to see the maps that I was working on.
Kostadis Roussos: So, so… So, you know…
Wade Brown: Story checks out.
David Mendenhall: Sure.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Wade Brown: Is it too much to ask for just a quiet existence for Soma?
Wade Brown: And she'd just go back into the woods.
David Mendenhall: The Google spreadsheet is not working for me.
Wade Brown: -Oh.
David Mendenhall: Everything else is working.
Wade Brown: Oh, wow, yeah, I'm getting a long loading bar on this.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Gary Young: name.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, ever since Gary left… ever since Gary left Google, things have gone to shit.
David Mendenhall: Yep, pretty much.
Gary Young: Sure.
Wade Brown: They were going to shit before he left, but, you know…
Kostadis Roussos: You know, he's our friend. Oh, yeah, you're, you're… yeah, sorry.
David Mendenhall: We can't play if we don't have our initiative tracker and our quests.
Gary Young: It's loaded now. It loaded now.
David Mendenhall: Oh god.
Gary Young: It says, open the last synced version due to poor connection.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, I've got nothing.
David Mendenhall: Google's down.
Wade Brown: It, it in fact is, yeah.
David Mendenhall: Bound detector says…
Wade Brown: Oh, I already linked it, yeah, it's there.
Wade Brown: Lots and lots of reports in the last,
David Mendenhall: Google Drive… Possible problems with Google Drive. I'm going to report a problem with login.
Gary Young: Well, if it helps, this is…
David Mendenhall: For reporting, your report was successfully submitted.
Wade Brown: Mine too.
Kostadis Roussos: I wonder if you know…
Gary Young: didn't have it open, this is the direct URL.
David Mendenhall: Hmm…
Kostadis Roussos: We put the direction.
David Mendenhall: have used, roll 20 for all of our tracking.
Wade Brown: Is this an old sticking point of cont… or point of contention, whatever?
Kostadis Roussos: No.
David Mendenhall: No, not really.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, I was able to log in.
David Mendenhall: Really?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, but I got the open the last sync version due to poor.
David Mendenhall: Well, that's what Gary got, yeah.
Wade Brown: That just means it's using your local storage cache.
David Mendenhall: That's what Gary got. I don't… and I don't think I have anything on my cache.
Gary Young: Yeah, but, like, it won't matter if…
David Mendenhall: It's not gonna help, we're not gonna be able to, like, share the spreadsheet in any way, right?
David Mendenhall: Reach get our own copy instead of a shared copy in the cloud.
Wade Brown: Yeah, that's, these things happen.
David Mendenhall: Technology has failed us.
Gary Young: We're gonna go out. Go out.
Kostadis Roussos: the hell? I'm telling you, you guys were making fun of me, but, like, basically, login stopped working, and Gary worked on that area. You think I… like…
Wade Brown: So we can make fun of him.
David Mendenhall: It's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just saying, man.
David Mendenhall: Well…
Kostadis Roussos: I was actually cracking a joke, I didn't anticipate this actually being a thing.
David Mendenhall: Huh, yeah, it really did.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, this is really annoying.
David Mendenhall: Very annoying.
Gary Young: So if you take all of your experienced engineers who helped design and build the thing, and lay the.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, here it comes! Gary's going to explain it to us, yes.
Gary Young: And lay them off for cheaper, you know, like, brand new, hires.
Wade Brown: Or L.A.
David Mendenhall: Hiring. You should be using AI agents for everything.
Wade Brown: Yeah, have Jetsky do it all.
Gary Young: Then what you get is cheaper operating costs.
Gary Young: It's great.
David Mendenhall: You get cheaper operating costs, that's right, there you go.
Wade Brown: If you have no users, you have no operating costs.
David Mendenhall: There's that, too.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: We're going to shrink our way out of this problem.
Gary Young: Maybe we should hire a Kostadis to downsize the staff of this organization.
David Mendenhall: How do you downsize the user base, though? That's what I want to know.
Wade Brown: And shitification.
David Mendenhall: I don't know how effective that is, actually.
Wade Brown: I know, I see people put up with so much.
David Mendenhall: We really do.
Kostadis Roussos: Mail still exists.
Wade Brown: I gotta tell you, like, when I turned on this Roku TV, like, it's the first time I've watched a live tuner broadcast, and it must have been, like, 15 or 20 years. I'm like, holy shit, it's all ads and super low quality.
Wade Brown: And I don't mean the ads are local, I mean, like, everything looks like it's a crushed 720p or something like that. I'm like, people watch this?
David Mendenhall: I have something?
David Mendenhall: Do you guys have something?
Wade Brown: Oh, let me try again.
Wade Brown: Let's see.
David Mendenhall: It is…
Wade Brown: Hey, hey, I think I got it!
David Mendenhall: It worked. It worked.
Wade Brown: Alright, down to tech turn.
Kostadis Roussos: They, they called that one last engineer.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, they rolled back the,
Wade Brown: Well, we did see Gary just leave the room, I mean, were you out there just, like, turning off and on the Google router or something? Like…
David Mendenhall: the AI agent successfully recovered.
Wade Brown: We used to call AI agents BGP.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, well, it seems, yes, it seems to have recovered.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, but that didn't use inference.
Wade Brown: Mr…
David Mendenhall: So, it wasn't the same.
Kostadis Roussos: By the way, you know, OpenAI and… OpenAI and Anthropic are definitely trying to set the fastest record to convince the market that people should do everything in their power to regulate their business award that I thought Mark Zuckerberg would own for all time.
Wade Brown: Yeah, I love… I love Zuckerberg saying, like, Congress, regulate us, come on me, bitch! Regulate the entire.
Gary Young: Did we see… did anyone read the Hugging Face incident report?
Kostadis Roussos: Never mind the… yeah, the hug… did anybody read what happened with the Navier-Stokes thing?
Gary Young: No, I didn't read that one.
Wade Brown: Miss both of these.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh my god! I thought you guys knew what I was talking about. So, basically, what happened was, there was a mathematician who was working with a buddy of his at OpenAI on a proof of the… or the counter proof, I don't actually know, of the Navier-Stokes model, right? It's one of the Millennium Prizes, right?
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: And so, he… the guy hit upon a particular approach that nobody had… nobody was working on except him and his friend, and they were working on it on their own time, and they were using AI to essentially crank out the proof.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And then, all of a sudden, he hears that OpenAI is working on a similar proof, so yeah, he calls up and discovered that OpenAI was
Kostadis Roussos: working on it. At first, OpenAI said, no, no, no, the AIs figured it out entirely on their own. But after a bit of hemming and hawing, it was revealed that they had heard that he was using that approach, and they were using it as well, and they had unleashed, you know, 10,000 agents to go solve it.
David Mendenhall: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, fine. So far, so good. And then it gets ugly, because then they're like, well… he's like, okay, well, I'm gonna… they said this… he goes, this is very awful, did you… like, did you guys look at any of my data? He goes, no, we didn't. He goes, can you prove you didn't look at any of my data? They were like, no.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so basically, I don't know if you stole my proof, like, and you're choosing an approach that pretty much nobody but me and another guy were looking at. It was completely an accident! So, after a little bit of hemming and hawing.
Kostadis Roussos: They said, here, why don't you release your proof, and then we'll release ours.
Kostadis Roussos: And, you know, I don't remember the… but then… and then they were like, okay, I have even a better idea, why don't we just… you release one proof, and we'll just say we did supporting things, and you'll get all the credit, but drop the OpenAI guy.
Kostadis Roussos: That's co-author.
Kostadis Roussos: And then when he said.
David Mendenhall: Extortion! Always a.
Kostadis Roussos: Then they said, no. He said, why would you do that to ruin your career?
Gary Young: I, I linked the…
David Mendenhall: Don't be evil!
Kostadis Roussos: No, this…
Gary Young: I linked the Hugging Face report.
Gary Young: I recommend reading it all the way down to the end with their action items.
Gary Young: And as you read through the action items, the question you should be asking is.
Gary Young: You didn't have that already?
Kostadis Roussos: All these action items.
David Mendenhall: It was an anthropic mathematician, Levant Apulus.
Kostadis Roussos: Got it.
Gary Young: Sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: Where's the, where's the, what should I be looking at?
Gary Young: I put it in Discord.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, where should I read the things that they should have done?
Wade Brown: rode ahead.
Gary Young: Yeah, it's at the end.
Kostadis Roussos: The road ahead.
Gary Young: It's the route ahead, yeah.
Gary Young: Anyway.
Gary Young: Read your lick, but…
Wade Brown: D&D now, read later.
Gary Young: Yeah, D&D know.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, God.
Kostadis Roussos: You weren't doing that already?
Gary Young: Yeah, that's like…
Gary Young: So… so the reason I was reading this is because, you know, my family was like.
Gary Young: you know, looking at the press articles that were, like, afraid of AI, and I'm like, okay, well, let's just see what they actually did, and see what we do. And I'm like, I am more afraid of the humans than the AI.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep, yeah, that just convinced me of that. All right, okay, so when we last left our noble adventurers, and by noble, I mean Bukradin.
Kostadis Roussos: And Soma, actually.
Wade Brown: Yeah, I'm not…
David Mendenhall: Someone's doing pretty well.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, and Soma, that's at Bukradin and Soma, yes?
Wade Brown: She's not greedy.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, no, she's actually, she's actually moving the needle. She's, you know, she's… she's embraced…
Kostadis Roussos: Her inner goodness, right? Concern for the.
David Mendenhall: I mean, she's still pro-treasure, but, you know, nobody's.
Kostadis Roussos: I said, I said Vukradin and Sova.
Kostadis Roussos: They're good along different dimensions.
Wade Brown: Moral relativism.
Gary Young: Y'all need to get on any dimensions, maybe?
Kostadis Roussos: Valfine is currently offering people options.
Wade Brown: Rouss are just inherently evil, don't you know that? Like, all… in all of Kostadis' campaigns, Drous are just…
David Mendenhall: You say that you support Lathander, on the other hand, Lathander is dead. But, you know…
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, this is, like, God is dead. This is the.
David Mendenhall: I know, I know, that is one… I know the Nietzsche angle, I thought of all the angles.
Kostadis Roussos: He's…
Wade Brown: Get ahead of you, man.
Kostadis Roussos: I know that. I'm aware. I'm aware. Yes, alright. So, let's see here, roll 20…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, let me get to my roommate.
Kostadis Roussos: And… So, the last thing that happened was that you arrived at the Tavern of the Thousand Faces.
Wade Brown: Oh, right, we were poking our holes through the wall. Right.
Kostadis Roussos: And Brewberry had gone in, and you guys knew that inside the tavern, was,
Kostadis Roussos: what's his name? Was a Harp… was a Harper hangout.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: That's the, critical, detail.
Wade Brown: And somehow you think Harpers are bad, so…
Kostadis Roussos: No, okay, so I actually spent some time thinking about it, because I felt like, you know, I owed you guys better than Harper's Bad. So, I mean…
Kostadis Roussos: No, I mean, the only person I owed it to is myself, just to be clear.
Kostadis Roussos: I decided that the problem with, the… so the Harpers…
Kostadis Roussos: So, there's 3 levels of power in my campaign. There is concentrated power and diffused power. Diffuse power are armies that can occupy areas.
Kostadis Roussos: Concentrated power are, like, high-powered individuals, gods, etc, right?
Kostadis Roussos: So, any government has to have both assets for concentrated power and diffuse power.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And you… and so, the Harpers believe that diffuse power is intrinsically evil, because it imposes control.
Kostadis Roussos: We didn't die. That's right, so there are.
Wade Brown: perspective.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, their perspective.
Gary Young: What did she say?
Wade Brown: He wants Dave to die.
Kostadis Roussos: No shit, nobody died. That's what she said. Nobody. God, immediately, you think the worst of people.
David Mendenhall: It's okay.
Wade Brown: She always wished Seth on Dave!
David Mendenhall: It's not the worst, it's just padded record.
Wade Brown: Meganism.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, she says TPK. She's actually telling you.
David Mendenhall: She wants everybody to die.
Kostadis Roussos: She wants everybody… she wants me to be quiet, that's what she wants. All right, so the Harpers believe that diffuse power is intrinsically dangerous, and they're opposed to it. They believe that individuals with concentrated power are only the only guarantee of peace, because they can't control large numbers of people.
Kostadis Roussos: So they're opposed to governments for that reason. They're also opposed to the naturalists, because the naturalists believe, like, the most important diffuse power is nature. And they also hate the Zantarim, because the Zantarim believe that, no, no, concentrated power can rule, have diffuse power, as long as it uses other means, like economic power.
Gary Young: I kind of looks terrible.
Wade Brown: Pretty hypocritical.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Gary Young: Economic power is also diffuse power.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, yes. But it can be concentrated in the hands of a small number of people.
Kostadis Roussos: That's why they hate the Zantarim. The Zantarim believe in concentrated… people with concentrated power having to fuse power through…
Kostadis Roussos: You know.
Wade Brown: So, the harbors are Bitcoin bros, is what I'm hearing.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I guess so, you could call them that, right? But, but…
Wade Brown: Yeah, they're evil, we gotta kill them.
Kostadis Roussos: They're not evil. They're just… As they have a particular point of view.
Kostadis Roussos: That, you know, big government's bad.
Wade Brown: Yes, Bitcoin bro's gotta die.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, this was not where I thought this was gonna go, but apparently I better roll up some character sheets.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see… okay.
Wade Brown: Excuse me.
Gary Young: So we had also taken, Wade's Familiar, Soma's Familiar, and shoved it in the hole.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade Brown: It was relayed… it's what relayed back to us that there were Harper documents and stuff inside.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Wade Brown: And Brubbery found ale inside at the front door, so there's that.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Gary Young: I guess we know where he's gonna be during this, this session.
Wade Brown: Oh, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, all right. So, is, so does Brewberry… so do you guys follow Brewery, or do you guys stay outside?
Wade Brown: I…
Gary Young: I'll go with brewberry.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
David Mendenhall: Yeah… Let's go.
Wade Brown: Yeah, I mean, we know it's… we know it's in the back room, I guess.
Wade Brown: Doesn't really tell us much to stay outside anymore.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Interesting. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So for various inside, he's wearing one of his, prototypes,
Wade Brown: For sure.
David Mendenhall: You guys want me to… find the room stealthily?
Gary Young: You wanna do what again?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, hold on, let… just give you… give me a second to describe the scene, and then you can do whatever you want. Yes. Just give me a second, then you can…
Kostadis Roussos: He's staring at a mannequin, wearing a coat.
Kostadis Roussos: That's… and muttering, this is so… Soft.
David Mendenhall: Blueberry's doing this?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, he's holding the lining of the coat, and is very impressed with the softness of the lining.
Wade Brown: Charmin would be proud.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, he's, he's, Lenain… he's thinking… he's wanting to know where that came from.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, and so one of the bar keeps sees the three of you come in here.
Kostadis Roussos: looks at you and says, if you're here for the mirrors, they flatter selectively. If you're here for a drink, that is more reliably… more reliable.
Kostadis Roussos: It's his opening line. I don't know.
Wade Brown: He's rehearsed it.
Kostadis Roussos: He's wor- he's worked on it.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So there's some staff members here.
Kostadis Roussos: So you're in this sort of room with, with a bunch of people, and they're called kind of, like.
Kostadis Roussos: Soma… Soma… sorry, not Soma. Valfine can tell that they're sort of evaluating you.
Gary Young: Okay, I'll evaluate them back.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Wade Brown: You're…
Kostadis Roussos: You're evaluating the back.
Wade Brown: mutual evaluation.
Gary Young: I'm, I'm wearing my gleaming white, plate mail of lithander.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Wade Brown: Hmm, pardon.
David Mendenhall: 20 insight.
David Mendenhall: 23 insight and a 20 insight.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh my.
David Mendenhall: We should have lots of insights.
Wade Brown: Oh yeah? Let me get a 1, let's see.
David Mendenhall: Well, we know it's her worst.
Wade Brown: 24 net crit inside.
David Mendenhall: We have a lot of insight.
Wade Brown: What's going on here, Harper Teams?
Gary Young: It's many of their harpers, we know they're gonna value us.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so are you gonna say anything? Are you gonna open the conversation, or are you gonna frame the conversation?
Gary Young: I feel like I want to go up to the bartender and say, we're interested in shipping services.
Kostadis Roussos: The guy looks at you and say,
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, the shipping services. Well, Mel Gatner Gaster delivers on time, because everyone else pays for the privilege.
Gary Young: Yeah, Mark Aster is not really…
Kostadis Roussos: He pauses and goes, we deliver late enough that nobody can charge the village.
Gary Young: Nobody can charge the village?
Kostadis Roussos: He basically is saying that they deliver late.
Wade Brown: Yes. So it's…
Kostadis Roussos: They're a slow delivery, but they charge less.
Wade Brown: You deliver late, like, after dark.
Wade Brown: 2AM kind of thing?
Kostadis Roussos: They, they look at you.
Wade Brown: We've seen his guy, right? We've seen Denver, or whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you've seen Denver. They, they, they,
David Mendenhall: Denver…
Wade Brown: Then, to Denver.
Kostadis Roussos: Denbar. Denbar.
Kostadis Roussos: Denver Daggerford.
David Mendenhall: What did… what did we name him? Denbar, actually. That was the different name.
Wade Brown: I thought Denver was fine, but…
Gary Young: John Denver, it works, yeah.
Wade Brown: John Denver.
Kostadis Roussos: Denver, Colorado, there was a lot of Denbarring.
Gary Young: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so…
David Mendenhall: Deadvar. Deadvar.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me ask you a question. Now, so, so they're kind of, like, alluding to that they know things, but they're sort of waiting for one of you to, like.
Kostadis Roussos: Make the first move.
Gary Young: Well… We have concern that in the city,
Gary Young: House Bargaster has been, profiting off of the, recent disappearance of this, distribution network. And,
Gary Young: We're interested in restoring some status quo here.
Kostadis Roussos: Valfine's opening statement brings a smile to the bartender's face.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, he goes, Praised be the morning Lord.
Gary Young: Of course.
Kostadis Roussos: I knew, I knew you were… there were those… the Harpers, the seat wanted… had his doubts, but I knew you were a true cleric of Lathander.
Kostadis Roussos: And there's nothing wrong with a little bit of tough love for, for saving people.
Gary Young: Or a lot of Tesla.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you say that or not?
Gary Young: I'll go somewhere.
David Mendenhall: Probably would, yeah.
Wade Brown: Yeah, she… I think she believes in suffering.
Gary Young: It's important to make sure that people know where the power is.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Wade Brown: Oh, ho-ho!
Kostadis Roussos: So, do you say it or not?
Gary Young: aside.
Wade Brown: You're just trying to make an enemy here.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, so what did… what do you say? Sorry, I was trying to read the notes so I could figure out…
Gary Young: It's important that, that, that people understand how to use, how to use power.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, no, alright, that is… that happens to line up very well with Harper ideology.
Gary Young: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And the most important thing about using power is using it only against equally powerful things, and not using it for control.
Kostadis Roussos: Says the Harper, back to you.
Gary Young: I think the mean thing is that,
Gary Young: we need to stamp out the, those who would do evil in this town, because that, those are the enemies of Luthander.
Kostadis Roussos: he smiles, he smiles and says, hold on, there's somebody who wants to talk to you. You notice the room suddenly deflates in terms of, like, everybody, everybody wanting to, you know, the tension deflates.
Gary Young: Oh, as in… Like, I stepped in something, or… No, you said that.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, some… you stepped out of some… out of something.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, every step.
Kostadis Roussos: People didn't know.
David Mendenhall: No one's gonna kill us now.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Kostadis Roussos: No, they were trying to figure out which way you landed.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: And so they've, you know, they've decided that you've landed in the good… that you've landed in the good path.
Gary Young: And then I have some questions for them later, too.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, abe…
Kostadis Roussos: elderly gnome… no, an elderly human, walks up from upstairs and very pedantically is wearing a Harper pin on him.
Kostadis Roussos: Brewberry, of course, at this point in time.
Kostadis Roussos: It demands to know where exactly they get the fabric for that cloak.
Gary Young: And he's also demanding for another beer.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes at the same time.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm imagining Blueberry taking that swatch and going like this, and, like, comparing it against…
Kostadis Roussos: Comparing it again, and ask… he's, he's like, he's starting to demand, where did they get this?
Kostadis Roussos: They inform him that,
Kostadis Roussos: that they can provide such a swath, this fabric to them, but it could not go through the Mergaster routes.
Kostadis Roussos: That's something for, him to think about later.
Wade Brown: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: I can imagine… You know, he does his usual intimidation schtick, but the Harpers are demonstrably unimpressed.
Kostadis Roussos: We will pause him here. All right. So, the Harper seats, says, points you to one of the tables, and asks you to sit down.
Gary Young: Bye.
Kostadis Roussos: You sit down. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: And so,
Kostadis Roussos: She asks, she… she explains that, to Brewberry that she offers shipping services that work around the current stranglehold that House Margaster has on the shipping routes.
Wade Brown: Care to say a little more?
Kostadis Roussos: She goes…
Kostadis Roussos: Here's the deal. We had a route. We operate the food route to break Bargaster and Zentarm pricing.
Wade Brown: Mmm.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Wade Brown: So they're not doing this in conjunction with Mergaster.
Kostadis Roussos: No! He looks at, no, we're not doing this in conjunction with Margaster. Margaster's trying to use their control of the… the trade routes to grab control of the city.
Kostadis Roussos: What they want to do, they create contracts, and those contracts have holes and details, and before you know it, you're under their thumb.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Wade Brown: Yep, that sounds like that.
Gary Young: Well, sounds like ambience, yep.
Wade Brown: They're Cambians?
Wade Brown: Spoiler!
Kostadis Roussos: They can be this offspring of devils or demons, yes. They go, really?
Kostadis Roussos: That's not what we heard, but that's a talk conversation for another time.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Wade Brown: The better question is, why…
Gary Young: almost… go ahead.
Wade Brown: I wanted to know why… why turn to smuggling instead of trying to reopen the, the shipping portal?
Gary Young: Directly, yeah.
Wade Brown: I, I… You know, not one to beat around the bush here.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you don't want to beat a rush.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Wade Brown: I mean, if they want to… if they're worried about breaking Morganaster's power, right, like the…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so she goes, she goes, she turns to you and says, well,
Kostadis Roussos: Why don't we go after that? Well, that's exactly where you can come in.
Wade Brown: Oh, boy. Fetch quest.
David Mendenhall: It's okay. I'm listening.
Kostadis Roussos: And they look at Vukradin and say, yes, there will be fair trade gold.
David Mendenhall: How'd you know that I was… I didn't say anything about Fair Trade Gold. You know, sometimes, I just want to do the right thing.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, in that case, we don't have to pay you.
David Mendenhall: No, no, a nice donation to the Studio Fund would be very appropriate in this situation.
Gary Young: Yes, we accept fair trade gold.
Kostadis Roussos: Here she goes.
Gary Young: the Churchill theater.
Wade Brown: And good.
David Mendenhall: fund.
Wade Brown: NT.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, T will give you Soma. She claps her hand, and one of the waiters show up. Meanwhile…
Wade Brown: things.
Kostadis Roussos: Meanwhile, people walk in, and you notice how everybody's trying to make this place look as boring as possible.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? So they're, like, it's kind of one of those hiding in plain sight situations.
David Mendenhall: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes…
Gary Young: Causing problems for that.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Gary Young: Are we causing problems for that, for that?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, at one point, somebody does notice who you are, and the wait staff explained that, no, no, LaFander's death is having a private meeting, and this is not the time and place for people to get their,
Gary Young: Autographs.
Wade Brown: No autographs, please.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, they, this is, this is, you know, that, you know.
Gary Young: We're wearing our sunglasses. What?
David Mendenhall: We're all wearing.
Gary Young: Peranger.
David Mendenhall: Classes?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Wade Brown: Hmm…
Gary Young: And the gleaming white armor.
Wade Brown: I'm just… And the helm of intimidation, or whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes… They said, she goes, I'm glad you asked about the manifold.
Kostadis Roussos: We know the Commission is lying about the manifold.
Kostadis Roussos: And we know…
Gary Young: up.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait, what.
Wade Brown: What is the story on the… I guess I don't know what the Commission's story currently is. Have we gotten that?
Kostadis Roussos: The commission… the Commission's story is that… Broke for repairs.
Wade Brown: Temporarily out of order, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade Brown: I don't even know if we'd heard that yet, so that's interesting. So they don't even have a story, they just have an excuse.
Gary Young: Beauties.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, they've been claiming that it's going to be repaired. It's been a 10-day. It's been a while, and it hasn't been repaired.
Kostadis Roussos: And then, the guy who's supposed to repair it disappears.
Wade Brown: Coincidence?
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Wade Brown: Can you tell us anything about the guy who was supposed to repair it?
Kostadis Roussos: We think it's a person who knows what's going on, and that is the person we give the ninth crate to that is in the sewers.
Wade Brown: Yeah, did we ever get the DL? I guess Picardin didn't really come back with any info, did he?
David Mendenhall: No, but we suspect the 9th grade is going to the gnome.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. So she more or less confirms it. But she then says.
Kostadis Roussos: We've been trying to follow the collector, but there are these spiders.
Kostadis Roussos: I wouldn't call them spiders, they're… they look like spiders, they have all sorts of weird colors and shapes, and they don't have a spider's head. Instead, where their neck is, is a mouthful of teeth. And they move in a natural ways, and their spider webs are…
Kostadis Roussos: Not… are all sorts of glimmering colors.
Gary Young: Do I know what these things are?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, you recognize them as Riftweavers.
Wade Brown: Yeah, they're blinking in and out of existence, basically.
Gary Young: We've seen those before.
Kostadis Roussos: Excellent!
Gary Young: But this does get to the next topic.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Gary Young: The next topic is… Do you know anything about the drow that has been…
Gary Young: Communicating with Lord Nevermender.
Kostadis Roussos: No, we haven't. That's a new rumor.
Gary Young: Well, the previous time we encountered these types of spiders, it was associated with a trowel.
Gary Young: That was, causing some mischief.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes… the seat looks at you and goes, you're talking about drow and mischief.
Kostadis Roussos: And she realizes she's talking to a drow.
Wade Brown: Oops.
Kostadis Roussos: there's a pause, you know, as she realizes that racial stereotyping is always bad, but at the same time, she feels compelled to acknowledge that stereotypes exist for a reason, and just because… just because certain societies have a predilection towards creating chaos and mayhem, but those are societies that embrace Lot's teaching, and clearly you don't… she's like, you know that moment when somebody's trying to explain that they're not a racist?
Gary Young: tests. Right.
Kostadis Roussos: That goes on for a few, that goes on for a bit.
Gary Young: We need to take down this drow.
Gary Young: To show them that.
David Mendenhall: What?
Gary Young: office.
David Mendenhall: You want to take down Lord Nevermember's Drow?
Gary Young: Well, it's probably my sister.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you say that out loud, or do you keep that… you could keep that on the down low?
Gary Young: That's fine.
Gary Young: Probably my sister.
Kostadis Roussos: Who is yours?
Gary Young: Take her down to show that Walt is weak.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, the Harper seat goes, I don't think there is anyone who's, who's,
Kostadis Roussos: I do not know of any drow that is in the inner circle of, of Lord Neverm…
David Mendenhall: you really are out of the loop. You don't know about this, you don't know about the Cambia and Markasters, you guys don't know anything that's going on. And you got us going to look for the gnome. The only thing you know is that the Bimbo the gnome is living in the.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, Bimbo who?
David Mendenhall: That's his name, Bimbo.
Gary Young: You don't even know his name.
David Mendenhall: Another thing you didn't know.
Kostadis Roussos: She drinks a little bit, smiles.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Alright, so… I updated our quest.
Kostadis Roussos: So yeah, so she went… what she wants… what she explains is… she explains that the spiders have recently appeared, ever since the guy who ran the manifold… since the manifold shut down.
Kostadis Roussos: Or rather, not since the manifold shut down, since that, the mechanic disappeared, and as a result of the mechanic's disappearance, the passageway that the Harpers were using for supplying food has become extremely dangerous, and if somebody doesn't go deal with that, they're going to be in trouble.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? What they explain is, they explain, they pause and explain. They say, it was part… it was part of a passageway that nobody went down.
Kostadis Roussos: There was some kind of weird magic that affected people.
David Mendenhall: What kind of manager would say more.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, it made people very uncomfortable.
David Mendenhall: comfortable.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Wade Brown: mildest.
Gary Young: These, strange devices that, my sister tends to get her hands on.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so she's like, your sister, you keep talking about your sister, like, who is your sister?
Gary Young: Elektra?
Kostadis Roussos: Never heard of it.
Gary Young: Box.
Gary Young: Huh?
Kostadis Roussos: You tell her your house name?
Gary Young: satori, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: They, they look… she looks at you.
Kostadis Roussos: And says, I thought they were dead.
Gary Young: Ugh, you know.
Wade Brown: Okay.
Gary Young: It is often convenient to be regarded as dead.
Kostadis Roussos: She pauses and goes, I think I'll have to update some people on their… on their threat levels.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Gary Young: So, I will, take out a piece of paper, MSA.
Gary Young: There you go.
David Mendenhall: Another thing that the Harpers didn't know…
Wade Brown: Heh.
Gary Young: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: What does the piece of…
Wade Brown: Our information gatherers are…
David Mendenhall: I'm not… I'm not very impressed with the… the income of the Harpers.
Gary Young: The piece of paper is our bill for all the information.
David Mendenhall: Oh, this one meeting was very useful for you, wasn't it?
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, first of all, we knew about the Sartora's disappearance and non-disappearance before you walked in through this door. It's not like… she, like, she gets really pissed, and it's like, it gets all huffy-puffy.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh.
David Mendenhall: So you do know things, you just don't want to tell me that you know them.
David Mendenhall: Hmm, I see how it is.
Kostadis Roussos: She smiles again.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: Did you go deeper.
Kostadis Roussos: You get the impression that she's not… she's not forthcoming with information, but she does say.
Gary Young: Insight is 28.
Wade Brown: Last item in 2028.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you're… that's what your insight reveals.
David Mendenhall: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: that she actually knows a lot more than she's leading on, but she's trying to figure out what you know. She does… but before anything happens, she turns to,
Kostadis Roussos: to Soma, and says, that,
Kostadis Roussos: You know, you should give your friend Lim the benefit of the doubt. She's been working for us for years.
Wade Brown: How long…
David Mendenhall: the harbor?
Wade Brown: Yeah, how long is the, the, thing been shut down.
Wade Brown: I keep forgetting what it's called.
Kostadis Roussos: the manifold.
Wade Brown: The manifold, thank you. How long has the manifold actually been shut down?
Kostadis Roussos: And now I… now I have…
Wade Brown: Just weeks? Okay, so Lim's been working with them far, far in advance of this, got it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes.
Wade Brown: I, I don't know how to take that.
Wade Brown: I… Lim is not the person I remember.
Kostadis Roussos: And, and he… and, what's her name? The Harper goes, and you are certainly not… the…
Kostadis Roussos: Torto Lim described you as.
Wade Brown: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: Both of you are.
Wade Brown: Time changes us all.
Kostadis Roussos: We thought… we thought you were going to become a naturalist.
Kostadis Roussos: And a threat, and a threat. Instead, you became, as she points out your staff, quite the determined interventionist.
Wade Brown: That just sort of happened underneath me.
Kostadis Roussos: I… Excuse me.
Wade Brown: The times make the turtle, not the turtle makes the times.
Kostadis Roussos: Apparently, apparently.
Kostadis Roussos: She's definitely… she definitely… you definitely get the impression that,
Kostadis Roussos: Lim was thinking you were going to be a naturalist, and was trying to pump you for information.
Kostadis Roussos: Because that's what Harpers do.
Wade Brown: Yeah, so when we walk in, they're all freaked out about us, huh?
Wade Brown: queen naturals. But she knows I'm not a naturalist.
Kostadis Roussos: No, yeah, that's what I'm saying, she's just saying you've changed quite a bit.
Wade Brown: Yeah, we've had our run-ins with some of those naturalists, they're, they sounded good on paper.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, they did sound good on paper.
Wade Brown: I think they want the world to be destroyed, which… yeah.
Wade Brown: Kinda, kinda, kinda like to live here.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, he goes, I completely, we completely agree. And that is why, Soma, I think you need to give your friend Lim a bit of a break.
Wade Brown: Because she gets…
Wade Brown: I mean, I'm not… I'm not giving her much of a hard time, it just, you know…
Wade Brown: Had different expectations for her.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, well, you know, I've just… you might want to go talk to her later. Meanwhile, she… then she pauses and goes, my… my… my… and there ends my friend therapy for the year.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, so she goes, so go… so you, you now…
Kostadis Roussos: I've given… been told to go deal with this spider passageway and an entrance to it, which happens to go through the were-rats territory.
David Mendenhall: But they want us to,
Kostadis Roussos: They also want you to…
David Mendenhall: They also want us to go in and clear out, though.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: Alright, so we've got… we've gotta… we gotta do the sewers. We've gotta go see Lord Nevermember tonight for dinner.
David Mendenhall: Tomorrow night, we have to perform at the Common Chord.
David Mendenhall: And we still haven't seen Lord… Lammy for tea.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: But now's a good time to go deal with the,
Wade Brown: We have a full social calendar.
Kostadis Roussos: the spiders.
David Mendenhall: Why is this a good time for the spiders? I'm gonna be really dirty for dinner.
David Mendenhall: When you're gonna go meet Lord Nevermember, you don't wanna have, like, blood and spider guts all over you.
Kostadis Roussos: She says, we have… we have places for you to wash up afterwards.
David Mendenhall: You gonna wash my clothes, too?
Kostadis Roussos: She looks at your clothes and says.
Kostadis Roussos: We can even get you some better ones.
Wade Brown: Fair trade clothes?
David Mendenhall: Yeah, where did you get them from?
Kostadis Roussos: We paid for them, like everybody else.
Gary Young: Okay, clothes, or performance costumes?
Kostadis Roussos: Beautiful.
David Mendenhall: Tomorrow night. We're performing tomorrow night. Tonight is Lord Member Remember.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, she goes, she goes, we're Harpers, we have disguises. We'll find something that makes you look even more incredible, Vukraden.
David Mendenhall: Are you patronizing me?
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, absolutely not. You are, in fact, the incredible Vukradin.
David Mendenhall: Well, since you seem to know so many things…
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: How is it that I'm somehow now famous?
Wade Brown: Good question.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, I haven't really thought about that.
Gary Young: Maybe you're being manipulated.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, like I said, I haven't really thought about that.
Kostadis Roussos: It is true.
David Mendenhall: You don't.
Kostadis Roussos: It is true, the stories of your… the stories of your, refusal to take gold, your singing, your sudden adoption by the, the order of the gauntlet.
David Mendenhall: Order of the gauntlet.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? The sudden appearance of a new cult of Lathander where there had never been one.
Wade Brown: And don't forget Universal Basic Treasure.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, that definitely got everybody talking.
Kostadis Roussos: And certainly… and then there was… and then there was the, the story of the drow.
Kostadis Roussos: who was the cleric of Lathander.
Kostadis Roussos: That got tongues wagging. And finally, there was the defeat of the dragon, so I don't know, there's just been a lot of different stories that all seem to converge.
Wade Brown: Isn't it usually bards that carry these stories? You've been performing on the side, maybe?
David Mendenhall: Not me.
David Mendenhall: Alright.
David Mendenhall: Let's go kill some spiders.
David Mendenhall: It's been, like, 3 months since we had a combat.
Wade Brown: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I keep throwing them at you, you guys keep walking away from them.
David Mendenhall: Oh, is that right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, like, I was about to… I offered you a combat here, and you're like, why should we go do that? Let's go do something else.
David Mendenhall: Alright, we're long rested before you go in, guys. Make sure you are long-rested.
Wade Brown: Alright.
Gary Young: I'll remind you already.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Gary Young: I'm all ready.
Kostadis Roussos: Who are already, like, does everybody remember all their character attributes?
Wade Brown: No, I'll figure it out.
David Mendenhall: I'll figure it out.
David Mendenhall: I don't think I'm gonna need hold person for spiders.
Wade Brown: I'll turn into a spider and dance with them.
David Mendenhall: Something fiery would be good.
Wade Brown: Oh, shoot, level 7 is…
David Mendenhall: Only I had Fireball.
Kostadis Roussos: Roots.
David Mendenhall: Oh, that's slow. Slow's useful.
David Mendenhall: Fusion, maybe?
David Mendenhall: The Cloud of Daggers is such a small area of effect.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let me get…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Freedom.
Kostadis Roussos: book.
David Mendenhall: I'm done.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Tell me when you guys are ready.
Wade Brown: I am, but…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. Okay, you ready?
David Mendenhall: Yeah, no problem.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, I thought you were, like,
David Mendenhall: I'm just, I'm just, min-maxing over here, but I'll be fine.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, that's why I didn't want to… I didn't want to interrupt the min-maxing, I know how much some players enjoy that.
Wade Brown: Got your two requisite levels in Fighter for Action Surge for that?
Kostadis Roussos: Dude.
David Mendenhall: Not doing that, not doing… I'm not doing… I'm just doing spells right now.
David Mendenhall: Alright, we'll try this.
Wade Brown: I know, but you could, you know, do, like, Sorcerer with two levels and fire, or in Fighter.
David Mendenhall: Oh, I know, I know.
David Mendenhall: I do that kind of thing.
Kostadis Roussos: He's trying to tell me.
David Mendenhall: in Baldur's Gate.
Wade Brown: Had a cheese mode every encounter, because, you know.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you're in the sewers.
Kostadis Roussos: This has got a lot of more passageways and whatnot. In this particular case, this is the only passageway you see.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, and standing, you head down, and there is Arsok, and his gang, the Dead Rats.
David Mendenhall: That's the name of the gang? Yeah. It's the Dead Rats.
David Mendenhall: I thought it was…
Wade Brown: Remember the Rat Pack?
David Mendenhall: at PAC. That's so much better.
David Mendenhall: You gotta go with that.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, does the crowd and suggest that?
David Mendenhall: It sounds like Soma suggested it. It's a great suggestion.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I know, but you're Rakuten, and she's just Soma.
Wade Brown: Oh, shit.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you know…
Wade Brown: Just so long.
David Mendenhall: Alright, the wrap pack it is.
Kostadis Roussos: It's the dead rats, man!
Wade Brown: We can do the Dead Rat Pack, how about that?
Kostadis Roussos: because, like, Rat Pack is kind of like calling it total…
Wade Brown: Choose your next word carefully.
Kostadis Roussos: The most amazing creature in divine grace.
Wade Brown: Darn tootin'.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. He goes, he looks at you, he's pleased to see you.
Kostadis Roussos: But he's also a little bit disappointed to discover an armed expedition has shown up.
Kostadis Roussos: And the first words out of his mouth are, Found yourself, then.
Kostadis Roussos: Remember, you'd lost your… you had been lost.
Wade Brown: Oh, Buchar,
David Mendenhall: Oh, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Found yourself.
David Mendenhall: Well, you're the one who sat us down here.
David Mendenhall: We had a whole conversation about it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I know! He's looking at… but you came around, you came around, with a few more people.
David Mendenhall: Well, you didn't expect me to kill all these spiders by myself, did you?
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know what I expected.
David Mendenhall: No.
Kostadis Roussos: Anyway… So, look, I need you… so you're gonna go clear out the spiders?
David Mendenhall: I suppose.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: And, we never…
Wade Brown: messing with all the trade routes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, it's like, that… that… those spiders have been blocked. So, the passageway…
Kostadis Roussos: The passageway… there was a passageway past that location, which had Nobody wanted to go down.
Kostadis Roussos: And… The spiders have taken residence up in a junction.
Kostadis Roussos: That goes down our passageways.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, we just need you to go deal with the spiders.
Kostadis Roussos: And, come back, give us our money, we'll give you the money.
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at you, and he says, 200 gold pieces?
David Mendenhall: 250.
David Mendenhall: What, did you have another party of adventurers that was gonna clear out yourself for you?
Wade Brown: He's just littered with, willing people.
David Mendenhall: Do you have a lot of leverage here that I wasn't aware of?
Kostadis Roussos: Like…
David Mendenhall: 250. We'll see ya.
Kostadis Roussos: Jesus!
David Mendenhall: We'll be back soon.
David Mendenhall: I got a date with the Lord tonight.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
David Mendenhall: I got a date with the Lord tonight, we'll be back soon.
Kostadis Roussos: He'll be back soon. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, let me get my map, alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you head down the hallway, beautiful.
Wade Brown: And, we fling the familiar ahead just for, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: Shits and giggles.
Wade Brown: Well, you know, making sure that it spots spiders before we get caught, all that stuff.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just make sure.
Wade Brown: Let's see…
David Mendenhall: Finally.
Kostadis Roussos: Can you guys see… can you guys see anything?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, huh.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just make sure, because I just realized I haven't used dynamic. I… the other person who hasn't done very much is Tender.
Kostadis Roussos: And I forgot to put on explore mode, that's what I forgot to.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
David Mendenhall: Oh, suddenly the map has changed.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, because I was, I had not set up… I had not,
David Mendenhall: Okay, now we're back here.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I just was just to show you what I just realized, I didn't…
David Mendenhall: The nice thing about a 5-foot passageway… is…
Kostadis Roussos: It's not a fight.
Kostadis Roussos: It's a 15 foot.
David Mendenhall: Oh, it's 15 feet, I see.
Kostadis Roussos: And don't pay too much attention to this, the map… the battle map is gonna be looked slightly differently.
David Mendenhall: Okay…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
David Mendenhall: It's new white.
Wade Brown: to see graph paper.
David Mendenhall: Month.
Wade Brown: We just see graph paper.
Kostadis Roussos: That's the problem.
Wade Brown: First, it was Google Drive.
Kostadis Roussos: What the hell? I just spent, like, a non-true amount of time drawing this map.
David Mendenhall: There's nothing.
Kostadis Roussos: I know! That's really effin' annoying.
Wade Brown: Language?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, Soma. I'm sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: I gotta be careful. We gotta use the right language in front of someone. All right, give me, like, 2 seconds to draw… I literally spent quite a bit of time drawing this map.
Wade Brown: Summer.
Kostadis Roussos: But, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Most of the time trying to decide what the map would be, so I can do this very quickly.
Wade Brown: Just make it up as you go.
Kostadis Roussos: Exactly.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so we'll have to do.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay…
Kostadis Roussos: And, here, let me show you what the…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so this is.
Wade Brown: That's perfectly fine.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I know. So this is what it kind of is supposed to look like.
Kostadis Roussos: And… That's the wrong one.
Kostadis Roussos: And my icon… my tokens got lost, which is very annoying. That's okay. I have my tokens.
Kostadis Roussos: This can be done in a second.
Wade Brown: You can always buy more tokens.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I know.
Kostadis Roussos: We did just say that, right?
Wade Brown: Hey, isn't this the room where you meet Withers?
Wade Brown: No, not quite.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you just say that?
Wade Brown: It almost looks like it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you know.
Wade Brown: I mean, there's only so many ways to draw a dank dungeon.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So… Right.
Kostadis Roussos: So… There are… the spiders.
Wade Brown: That's a lot of spiders.
David Mendenhall: Before we go in…
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, let me just… one more thing I have to draw.
Kostadis Roussos: So there's this, essentially, and then there's the boss spider, which I will…
Kostadis Roussos: But over here, because I didn't have time to create an icon.
Wade Brown: Load-bearing spider.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you say load-bearing? I hate you.
Wade Brown: What?
Kostadis Roussos: Because, like, it's like the quintessential, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: word that the Infernal app uses.
Wade Brown: Oh, that, I… yes.
Wade Brown: used to the joke of, oh, that boss was load-bearing, because when you kill him, the dungeon starts to crumble and fall apart.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just put some tokens…
Wade Brown: This predates my, you know, Kodi obsession.
Kostadis Roussos: I understand, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, nice party.
Kostadis Roussos: Except the party isn't all here.
David Mendenhall: Everybody gets bardic inspiration.
Wade Brown: Woohoo!
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, Cronin… Balfine Soma… And who else? Weberry?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okie dokie.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty. So, just to give you some… some lay of the land.
Kostadis Roussos: This is the middle area here, which, I'm gonna… It's full of water.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: There is a big boss spider standing over… standing,
Kostadis Roussos: Let's say, clinging on to a web.
Kostadis Roussos: Above the ground?
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just draw the web here.
David Mendenhall: Are there, like, webs all around?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I was about to draw that.
Wade Brown: What are we looking at for ceiling height here?
Kostadis Roussos: 25 feet.
David Mendenhall: Gary… What do you think about me blowing my fourth level? Gary, are you there? You listening?
David Mendenhall: What do you think about me casting Freedom of Movement on Blueberry?
Gary Young: Sounds great.
David Mendenhall: It's my only 4th level spell slot.
Gary Young: I have another, spell slot, but I wasn't gonna use Freedom of Movement.
Gary Young: Yeah, but, like, with all these webs, probably useful for him.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, so Brewberry gets freedom of movement, and that's good for 1 hour.
Kostadis Roussos: End of the whole, your character died.
Kostadis Roussos: Why do you keep saying that?
Kostadis Roussos: Just Mendenhall, not everybody. Yes, but we like… we like Mendenhall, and it's… we start…
Kostadis Roussos: Dave, I just said his character died.
Wade Brown: Davis's character.
Kostadis Roussos: Goodbye. Alright.
David Mendenhall: Good night!
Kostadis Roussos: So yes, this side has spidery webs on it.
Kostadis Roussos: And this side has a control system which can control the water, and you notice that water is slowly seeping into this area.
David Mendenhall: Okay, well…
Kostadis Roussos: Essentially, this.
David Mendenhall: Freedom of movement means that, breweries
David Mendenhall: Can swim as fast as he can walk.
Wade Brown: Right? Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: And the… Energy over here.
David Mendenhall: breathing types… we don't have anything that's for water breathing, right?
Kostadis Roussos: No, and the water is not that deep.
Kostadis Roussos: At the moment.
Wade Brown: not exactly water.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, you know, there is water substances in it.
David Mendenhall: Oh, yeah.
David Mendenhall: Alright, Brewery, charge! No, roll for initiative.
Wade Brown: Oh, right, right. Scott, it's been so long.
David Mendenhall: I know.
Kostadis Roussos: Do we know how to roll for initiative?
David Mendenhall: You got a 7.
Gary Young: Does Brewberry have advantage on Initiative for some reason?
Wade Brown: That's what I saw in the roll, but I don't know why.
Kostadis Roussos: He does, for one of his abilities.
David Mendenhall: Couldn't be.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Gary Young: Cool.
Wade Brown: Nifty.
Gary Young: 14 for him…
David Mendenhall: 14.
David Mendenhall: All right, did you want to put Steve?
Kostadis Roussos: these stat blocks.
David Mendenhall: The monsters on, with 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 spiders.
Kostadis Roussos: What'd you say?
David Mendenhall: Don't you want to put the,
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, let me.
Wade Brown: Versa, I mean…
Kostadis Roussos: I need to, I just get the… I just realized I don't have the stat block.
Kostadis Roussos: Or these spiders?
David Mendenhall: 26 hit points, no problem. AC14, it's easy peasy.
Kostadis Roussos: No.
David Mendenhall: No, I'm sure.
David Mendenhall: spiders?
David Mendenhall: Okay, Spider? I have a few more points.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, hold on.
Wade Brown: Probably call them Rift Weavers or something?
Kostadis Roussos: this.
David Mendenhall: We faced these in the, in the warehouse, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Do you face them?
Wade Brown: We had Rift and Gnomes, didn't we? No, that was in the Counting House.
Gary Young: Yeah, it was in that, dwarfish, citadel that had been… The deface.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, where we got… Is that where we got Boney?
Wade Brown: We got…
Kostadis Roussos: No, no.
Wade Brown: Before then…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, armor class 13, hit points 32.
Kostadis Roussos: Except… and the big boss is, 15 and 19.
David Mendenhall: Our class 13, hit points 32?
Kostadis Roussos: Yep, armor… and the other one's armor class 15, and hit points 95.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright…
David Mendenhall: Does the boss have a name?
Kostadis Roussos: Whit Rift Weaver Prime.
David Mendenhall: Love it.
Kostadis Roussos: the thing about.
Wade Brown: Got me rent a Tron, I don't know.
Kostadis Roussos: The thing they're beginning to realize is they don't really have a personality.
David Mendenhall: Personality.
David Mendenhall: They're spiders.
Wade Brown: Yeah, that's…
Kostadis Roussos: But yeah, but they're not… they don't behave like spiders. They, like, move in packs, they seem to be particularly interested in particular things. They're not…
Wade Brown: Sounds like a personality to me.
David Mendenhall: Okay, so, Blueberry, you could probably kill two of these in one round. Go for it.
Wade Brown: I think I'm…
David Mendenhall: We need… we need some initiative rolls, though.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Initiative.
David Mendenhall: Plus 2 on their initiative.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, let me just make sure that's correct.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, plus 2.
Kostadis Roussos: There should be 6 of them. 1, 2, 3, 4… One more, there's one missing.
David Mendenhall: Oh, yeah, you're right.
David Mendenhall: Congressman.
Kostadis Roussos: East.
Kostadis Roussos: Fine.
Kostadis Roussos: Hang on.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
David Mendenhall: torch.
David Mendenhall: Phase Spider 3.
Kostadis Roussos: Phase spider 3. Alright, what does phase spider 3 do?
Gary Young: By the way, I recommend not going in the room.
David Mendenhall: Oh, we need a roll-off. Bukradin.
Kostadis Roussos: against…
David Mendenhall: master.
David Mendenhall: 19?
Kostadis Roussos: 5…
David Mendenhall: Gotcha.
David Mendenhall: Sure, except for blueberry.
David Mendenhall: Brewery can go in the room.
David Mendenhall: And get surrounded.
Kostadis Roussos: R.
David Mendenhall: But he will not be in.
Gary Young: Yeah, I don't… I don't think you're gonna wanna go in the room.
Kostadis Roussos: Why?
Wade Brown: Why is that?
David Mendenhall: You're controlling brewberries, so you decide.
Gary Young: But he'll go after me, so…
Gary Young: Just so long as someone doesn't go in the room.
David Mendenhall: Fighter 3.
Wade Brown: Charge!
Kostadis Roussos: Spider 3, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so it will attempt to… I guess Soma's standing at the very, the very opening?
Wade Brown: Hey, Soma and Valfini appear to be in front. We wouldn't have had blueberry up front?
Gary Young: Yeah, I should probably fix that.
Wade Brown: I think it'd be Soma and Brewberry up front.
Kostadis Roussos: So in Berberg.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, number 3, attacks.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm sorry, it's a plus 4, 15.
Kostadis Roussos: Against, I guess, Brewberry. Once Brewberry's armor class?
Gary Young: Premier's armor class is… 15, I think?
David Mendenhall: Jeez.
Gary Young: 17.
Gary Young: I'll fix the tracker.
Kostadis Roussos: Because it says 15. Alright, that is a miss.
Gary Young: Okay.
David Mendenhall: That's it? Okay. Soma?
Gary Young: It's gonna have somewhere.
David Mendenhall: Oh, there's more. Alright. Layer actions.
Kostadis Roussos: No.
Kostadis Roussos: A bonus action.
David Mendenhall: Notice action.
Kostadis Roussos: a bonus action.
Kostadis Roussos: And it goes over here.
Kostadis Roussos: He sort of phases in and out.
Gary Young: Yep, that's not gonna help.
Kostadis Roussos: That's fine, I mean, whatever, I mean, I don't know what you're gonna do, like, yes, you're gonna do something amazing, like, I've…
Kostadis Roussos: I'm doing… the creatures only have so many thoughts. Okay.
Gary Young: It's fine.
Gary Young: Right, who's that?
Wade Brown: Selma.
Gary Young: Summer.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you tell Soma to rut, not rush in, or not?
Gary Young: Yeah, don't rush it. Don't rush it.
Wade Brown: Alright, we're Flaming Spear over here, though…
David Mendenhall: Labs on fire.
Wade Brown: That's the plan, just light everything up, and also the sphere is sort of a familiar that I can bounce around. I was pretty aware that…
Kostadis Roussos: So… alright. So how much damage does the Flaming Sphere do?
Wade Brown: It did, 7 damage, but it also, you know, sets ablaze things, and it's a…
Kostadis Roussos: Where'd you put it? Right there.
Wade Brown: Up here on number 1.
Wade Brown: So I need to… sorry, it's been a little while, I gotta remember how to find the, tokens.
Wade Brown: Just need a 5-foot radius.
Kostadis Roussos: Here you go.
Wade Brown: Yeah, it'll do. I can't move that, there we go.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, well, it's over there, right?
Wade Brown: Yeah, for now. I mean, next turn I'll move it, but whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so…
Wade Brown: He's over there, presumably setting things on fire, doing some minor damage to number 1. He has a DC safe.
Kostadis Roussos: What's the same?
Wade Brown: DC15 Dexterity?
Kostadis Roussos: Brilliant.
Kostadis Roussos: Makes a saving throw, so he doesn't take any damage. Does he take half damage?
Wade Brown: Fiddlesticks, let me double check.
David Mendenhall: D.
Wade Brown: It's… yeah, I always agree, I think it's half damage. Half damage, yeah, so he takes 3.
Kostadis Roussos: But because he's vulnerable to fire, he takes 7.
Wade Brown: Oh, wow.
Wade Brown: Charlotte.
Kostadis Roussos: Call from the last time.
Kostadis Roussos: That's why you used fire, right?
Wade Brown: I wanted to burn all the webs up so we could move around, yeah.
David Mendenhall: That's why I have a necklace of fireballs.
Kostadis Roussos: You don't have the necklace of Fireballs.
David Mendenhall: I know.
Wade Brown: Yeah, we gave it to April.
Kostadis Roussos: Brewberry says, we could have had the necklace of Fireballs.
Wade Brown: And then as a bonus action, I think I'm just going to, turn into a spider to join the, get that freedom of movement. Well, to also get freedom of movement on this stuff, because…
Kostadis Roussos: Got it.
Wade Brown: Alright, that's me.
David Mendenhall: surgeon.
Wade Brown: I'm not charging in yet, you know, presumably there's a bunch of fire spreading now, so I'm not gonna deal with it, but…
Kostadis Roussos: So, Soma's just gonna wait there patiently. All right.
Wade Brown: Well, I've got no more actions. I've done a spell and a shift and all, like, I'm good.
David Mendenhall: movement. You have movement, but you don't want to use it.
Wade Brown: I don't… Valfine is sitting here saying, stay the fuck out of the room. Staying out of the room.
David Mendenhall: Okay, Delphine's got a plan.
Wade Brown: Yeah, I will put the ball of fire in there, then I can control the ball of fire, that's it.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay. Valfini.
David Mendenhall: You're right, you're up, Velfina.
Gary Young: I'm going to cast Doomtide.
Gary Young: Okay, this dude type.
Kostadis Roussos: do.
Gary Young: Bad stuff.
Kostadis Roussos: Apparently…
Gary Young: 24 radius.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: So, would…
Gary Young: 3D.
Kostadis Roussos: want.
David Mendenhall: Inky fog.
Gary Young: mean, like, I can get 4.
Kostadis Roussos: No, they have to be half. You can get… the guy in the corner, you could not get. He's… there. You can get…
Kostadis Roussos: 3.
Gary Young: I can only get 3.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Gary Young: But they're, they're, they're large.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, but they're still not… it's still not half… it's still not half the square. Like, this one is not half, you'd have to be, like…
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see… let me just see, let me just see, let me just see. Here, this is where you have to place it. Alright, fine.
Kostadis Roussos: If you place it here, you can get 4.
Gary Young: Okay.
Gary Young: Wisdom Save DC15 for… 22 psychic damage.
Kostadis Roussos: BD20.
Kostadis Roussos: Lust. Okay, psychic damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, wisdom, saving throw, I'm going to assume. Do they have any resistances?
Kostadis Roussos: This definitely doesn't.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, he chooses.
Gary Young: So the fog is magical darkness, and lasts for the duration.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, right.
Kostadis Roussos: The Prime blows his saving throw, but chooses to pass it using his legendary resistance.
David Mendenhall: Nice.
Gary Young: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Gary Young: So, it takes, 11 Psychic.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, everybody else takes full psychic damage.
Gary Young: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And what else does this do?
Gary Young: On a failed save, you also subtract, 1d6 from your saving throws until the end of your next turn.
Kostadis Roussos: Got it, okay.
Gary Young: And…
Gary Young: I think I need to have it go just a little bit like this, because it will slowly… actually…
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Gary Young: Can I do… can I do like that?
David Mendenhall: Yeah, I think you should… I think you should do it like that.
Gary Young: Okay, so the main thing is that this, this gas cloud will slowly waft to the east every turn.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, we'll slowly waft… so it's a cloud that wafts to the east, is that what I heard?
Gary Young: Yeah, and it will…
Kostadis Roussos: Setting throws down by 5?
Gary Young: Yes.
Gary Young: That creature also makes the save when it moves in… when the sphere moves into its space, when it enters the sphere, or when it ends the turn inside the sphere.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, don't end the turn, don't start the turn.
David Mendenhall: Okay, but by the way, now I can't see anything, so I won't be able to target any creatures with my attacks.
Kostadis Roussos: You could target the Or… Is it a 20…
Wade Brown: Can you see through the fog, or just not into it, or…
Gary Young: It's in magical darkness.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, you can't…
David Mendenhall: Well, it's not my turn yet, we'll see what happens, you know.
Wade Brown: concentrate.
David Mendenhall: Long way.
Wade Brown: first.
David Mendenhall: It's a concentration spell, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Lots of things, lots of things can happen.
David Mendenhall: could still happen.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, blueberry's up.
Gary Young: Okay, so… brewberry… Can he, like, maybe… See the sky?
Kostadis Roussos: You can't see… if it's darkness, you can't see through it.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, I…
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, you, you, you…
Gary Young: Can't see that guy.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, like, alright, he can, but it's 3 quarters cover. How about I do it that way?
Gary Young: So…
Gary Young: So let's, let's say, you did damage to 1, 3, and the, and the boss, is that right?
Kostadis Roussos: I did, I don't… we… originally, we were gonna do a 3, 2, and 4.
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry. 3, 2, and 5, that was the original ones, then you moved it.
Gary Young: Okay, so… So, if we're doing 1, 3, and the boss.
Gary Young: Then maybe 4 is just a little bit outside of it, and then maybe he can see 4.
David Mendenhall: Move the… move the sphere up a little bit.
Kostadis Roussos: There we go.
David Mendenhall: Narrow.
Kostadis Roussos: There, then he can see them just fine.
David Mendenhall: I don't know.
Gary Young: Alright, now I need to apply the damage here, too.
Gary Young: So it was… Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: So, 1, 3, and the boss.
Gary Young: boss.
Kostadis Roussos: 2 and 5 should have no damage.
David Mendenhall: Yep.
David Mendenhall: Correct.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Gary Young: Okay.
Gary Young: And so then Brewberry will rage and attack 4.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Gary Young: Can you make them bigger?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, if he gets big, he's in the zone of horror.
Gary Young: Can he not, do it from outside of the room?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, he's got incredible reach.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Wade Brown: He's a man of many talents.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me send this to the back, order, send two back. Alright, there we go.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so he's over here.
Kostadis Roussos: he can out from over here. I guess he's got enough reach.
Kostadis Roussos: That would be inside the room. Like, from here, he can use his Hallbird because he's got enough reach.
Gary Young: So it can attack 4 from here, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, but he doesn't have to move, is my point.
Gary Young: Yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: He can attack literally from where he's standing. He doesn't have to move.
Gary Young: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: If he has to move, he gets inside of the radius. That was my only point.
Gary Young: Okay, so he makes…
Kostadis Roussos: miss.
David Mendenhall: So…
Kostadis Roussos: Congressman.
David Mendenhall: Or the plugin. No, no.
Kostadis Roussos: I think you, I think you rolled… I think you, yeah, two, two, two misses?
Wade Brown: Yeah?
Gary Young: You're welcome.
Wade Brown: Ovens.
Kostadis Roussos: Confirm you rolled two 11s.
Wade Brown: He did. There are two unique roles here.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, well, that was… after all of that amazing effort and planning.
David Mendenhall: Would you like…
Kostadis Roussos: Thank you.
David Mendenhall: Use your bardic inspiration?
Gary Young: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
David Mendenhall: less?
Gary Young: How about both?
Kostadis Roussos: So let's…
Gary Young: Okay, so there should be… 12 and 14? When does it?
Kostadis Roussos: So… No, no, it's 13, it's plus 2, right? Is that what you're getting from the plus?
Gary Young: A bless on the first one would make it 13.
David Mendenhall: Okay, so that's a hit, so don't use the bark inspiration, just hit 13.
Kostadis Roussos: The second one would also, if he used the Bardic Inspiration.
David Mendenhall: No, then he uses the Bless… use the Bless again, or you can only use it once per turn?
Gary Young: That's a good question.
Gary Young: Let's just double-check that.
Kostadis Roussos: To every attack roll.
Gary Young: Is it a reattach role?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I just… I just checked it.
David Mendenhall: Okay, so you didn't have to use the bargainpiration at all, so you've now hit on both.
Gary Young: Okay.
Gary Young: So, 13 and 15 on 4.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So 28 points of damage, right?
Gary Young: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Gary Young: So what's that for?
Kostadis Roussos: Sounds good.
David Mendenhall: Okay, good. Except for blueberry?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, spider number Tula.
David Mendenhall: Prior to.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
David Mendenhall: Bright or two cannot see through the magical darkness.
Kostadis Roussos: No, we cannot.
Kostadis Roussos: Much to his irritation.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
David Mendenhall: He should not walk through the darkness, or…
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no, he's teleporting, he's teleporting to the dark.
David Mendenhall: teleporting, sure.
Wade Brown: Yeah, they're, they're not…
David Mendenhall: Oh, yes, phase spider.
Wade Brown: Not of this world.
David Mendenhall: Yes, phase spiders.
Kostadis Roussos: And then it's going to… We're here…
Kostadis Roussos: And he's going to try to grapple Blueberry with his, spidery… With this spidery…
David Mendenhall: Feel free.
Wade Brown: Of all the ones to grapple.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, that's the only one I can grapple. The rest of you are hiding behind Brewberry.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Wade Brown: Rubri kind of grew up over me, didn't he?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm assuming you're kind of, like, underneath Brewberry, like, as a…
Wade Brown: I'm actually a giant spider, yeah, anyway.
Wade Brown: I don't remember what size it is.
Gary Young: So, the giant spider is, like…
David Mendenhall: You can go ahead, you can try to grapple, if you want.
Wade Brown: Oh, it's supposed to be large, anyway.
Gary Young: Does he roll a strength… an athletics check, or a strength check?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, I'm… I… it's a two-hit roll, hold on.
Gary Young: Okay.
Wade Brown: Thank you.
David Mendenhall: Do you see the note I just put in the… put in there, Gary, on freedom of movement?
Gary Young: 5 feet in the meantime.
Gary Young: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So you're still not visible into the room, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Rakuten, where are you? Like, can you just put yourself on the map?
David Mendenhall: I am on the map.
Kostadis Roussos: No, but, like, are you…
David Mendenhall: I'm right there.
Kostadis Roussos: You're right there.
David Mendenhall: That is me.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay. So, yes, they tried to, grab you.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, he attempts to grab you with his, his… his dry web.
Kostadis Roussos: Particularly dry-ish web that glimmers in the dark.
Kostadis Roussos: And…
Kostadis Roussos: That's a natural 20, so he does successfully grab you, but I'm assuming that your ring of… your free action makes it so that you are not grabbed?
Gary Young: The Freedom of Movement.
Gary Young: Automatically escape.
Wade Brown: At the cover.
Gary Young: That's the 5 movement.
Wade Brown: Oof, which…
Gary Young: Oh, absolutely.
Kostadis Roussos: Does it allow you to escape the restrained condition? Because it's not a grapple, it's a restrained condition.
David Mendenhall: Correct.
Kostadis Roussos: Does, yeah? I'm assuming it does.
Wade Brown: It costs 5 movement.
David Mendenhall: Any creature imposing the grappled condition.
Kostadis Roussos: No, there's not the grapple condition, this is the restrained condition.
David Mendenhall: It says, any non-magical restraint.
Kostadis Roussos: Fair enough.
Kostadis Roussos: This is non-magical.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, this is a spidery web. Alright, that's what he does.
Gary Young: Okay, so then he is… Restrained at the moment, but can spend 5 feet of movement to cancel it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade Brown: So until his turn, he'll be restrained.
Gary Young: And do I not get a grapple check?
Kostadis Roussos: No, it's a two-hit. You can break out of it afterwards.
Gary Young: Oh, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: It's not a grapple, it's a… ability. Roof.
David Mendenhall: Alright, Spider 5?
Kostadis Roussos: Brighter 5.
Kostadis Roussos: Spider 5.
Wade Brown: Oh, spider fight, spider fight.
Wade Brown: Sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: We'll also try to grab Blueberry.
Gary Young: Wow.
Kostadis Roussos: And Mrs.
Wade Brown: Eight arms and can't even broadside up a barn.
Kostadis Roussos: And then, number 1… We'll come over here.
Kostadis Roussos: We'll crawl to the surface.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see, so let me just make sure I got the whole distance thing right.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep. Comes over here.
Kostadis Roussos: And we'll attack… You get an attack, by the way,
Wade Brown: drama.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, what's his name?
Wade Brown: Oh, proverb.
Kostadis Roussos: Blueberry, because he entered the zone of blueberry death.
Wade Brown: Right.
Gary Young: 15 slashing on one.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: And…
Gary Young: Which killed it.
Kostadis Roussos: No, one hasn't been hit. Oh, it's dead?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so it dies on the way there. Alright.
Gary Young: By the way, there's a phantom spider underneath Work.
Kostadis Roussos: I just deleted him.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, next.
Gary Young: Okay, for cotton?
David Mendenhall: Yeah… I was thinking about, what should I do?
Gary Young: Did you cast Freedom of Movement yet?
Wade Brown: He did it before the bus.
David Mendenhall: It's not a concentration spell, I did it before the combat started.
Wade Brown: And it's a 1 hour duration.
David Mendenhall: for one hour.
Gary Young: Okay.
David Mendenhall: So, you're good.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, we should do the Craden's Round and stop, because it's 10.30.
Wade Brown: It is indeed.
Kostadis Roussos: We're so slow with combat.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, we are.
Wade Brown: Rusty.
Wade Brown: Here, give us, you know, some slack, man.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm giving you slack, I'm just laughing, because, like, I kept trying to throw combat at you guys, and you kept, like, walking away from it.
Wade Brown: Do you want us to just go murder Hobo? Like…
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no. I thought GMs hate that. No, I… I don't hate that.
Kostadis Roussos: Beautiful.
Kostadis Roussos: I just think there are consequences to going Wanderer Hobo.
Wade Brown: Not usually.
David Mendenhall: Is it possible for me to move here?
Kostadis Roussos: Absolutely.
David Mendenhall: Am I, like…
Kostadis Roussos: You are out of the zone. It is…
David Mendenhall: Yeah, I'm not, like, subject to psych- psychic damage.
Kostadis Roussos: No, you're not subject.
David Mendenhall: Exactly, damaged it.
Kostadis Roussos: Just again, to remind you, the rule is half the square.
David Mendenhall: cone…
David Mendenhall: Like that? Yep. Does that hit 2 spiders, or 3?
Kostadis Roussos: 2.
Wade Brown: Two, for sure.
Kostadis Roussos: It has to cover half the token.
Gary Young: So, number 4 has 4 hit points.
Gary Young: And number 2 is false.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so what's the damage?
David Mendenhall: Dc15 deck save for 24 damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, the first one's dead. They've died again.
Wade Brown: cheat.
Kostadis Roussos: And the second one take, 24 points of damage.
David Mendenhall: Alright, so 4 is dead, and 2 takes 24.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Gary Young: I'll apply the 24.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
David Mendenhall: And then, having… No longer being threatened, I will retreat.
Kostadis Roussos: retreat.
Wade Brown: He bravely ran away.
David Mendenhall: Oh, yes.
Wade Brown: No, that's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: and we'll stop here.
Wade Brown: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me insert a run row above.
David Mendenhall: One is dead, and 4 is dead?
Gary Young: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Of… Yeah, Ford is dead. Alright, there we go.
Kostadis Roussos: Is Boney with us, or he's not in the sewers?
Wade Brown: I guess we just didn't bring up.
David Mendenhall: I wouldn't think he's a bee in the sewer, no, that's.
Wade Brown: How do you get a horse in and out of the sewers?
David Mendenhall: Yeah, exactly.
Wade Brown: He's not like a Pokeball kind of horse, like, he's a… he's a flesh and blood… well, no flesh or blood, but you know.
David Mendenhall: He's a skeletal horse.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, you know, maybe you could collapse them into, you know, bone structure and…
Wade Brown: It becomes like a, A jigsaw puzzle every time to reassemble.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Wade Brown: Where does the ulna go?
Wade Brown: Next to the tibia, is it?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, we could do the Rift Weaver's attack so that we at least get it out of the way.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Wade Brown: Yeah, leave it at the top of the round.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, how's he gonna annihilate us?
Kostadis Roussos: He's not gonna annihilate you.
Kostadis Roussos: This was not meant to be a particularly challenging combat. This was meant to be a,
Wade Brown: We're already bonked two of them, right? Like…
Wade Brown: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty, so… Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so what he does… is a first. Teleports.
Kostadis Roussos: 40 feet, and lands right on top of Gridan.
Kostadis Roussos: You notice that they seem to have a particular obsession for you.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Wade Brown: They like his music, he's popular.
David Mendenhall: That must be it.
Gary Young: So there's no attack opportunity then, right?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, because it's teleportation.
Kostadis Roussos: And then… Alright, and then…
Kostadis Roussos: Tech he does.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, he will then attack you.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, and then he will attempt to attack you.
David Mendenhall: Good luck.
Kostadis Roussos: Like I said, you will attempt.
Wade Brown: Fun of his mother.
Kostadis Roussos: You know.
Wade Brown: Or whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: Your mother only laid one egg.
Kostadis Roussos: It says.
Kostadis Roussos: In spider parlance.
Kostadis Roussos: That's critical.
David Mendenhall: Nope. We're going to re-roll.
Kostadis Roussos: There it is.
David Mendenhall: I'll use my reaction.
Kostadis Roussos: That's a 13.
David Mendenhall: That is a miss.
Kostadis Roussos: That is a miss.
Wade Brown: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: And now we will end here.
Wade Brown: Up initiative.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
David Mendenhall: And I get to grant somebody advantage. Who wants advantage?
Wade Brown: Brewery, I always.
David Mendenhall: Brewery! Take advantage.
Kostadis Roussos: And since, apparently, since we're having the combat in the tunnel, let me just draw the tunnel.
Gary Young: Oh.
Gary Young: tunnel.
Gary Young: So then, Valfin is not in the top. Okay, alright.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm kind of putting you guys all here.
Gary Young: Does that mean that Soma is on the ceiling?
Wade Brown: Sure.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, she… oh yeah, someone's on the ceiling…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, yes, Tom is on the ceiling, the other spider's on the ceiling, blueberries on the ground.
Wade Brown: Was there no ignition of the webs, by the way, from fire?
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Wade Brown: Was there nothing lit on fire?
Kostadis Roussos: We haven't gotten… I figured we would do that…
Wade Brown: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Since it, like, hasn't really affected anything yet.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, it hasn't really.
Wade Brown: Well, I mean, it changes motion for people going in there, but yeah, nobody's gone in, so…
Kostadis Roussos: We can do it later. But just in case you're wondering, the rules on it are, like, 5 feet every round.
Wade Brown: I see.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
David Mendenhall: Wow, that's slow.
Wade Brown: Well, yeah, but the thing also moves 30 feet every round, so, you know, I'll light my multiple fires for him to trek.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, so…
Kostadis Roussos: I will… I will check the… I will check the rules and see what… what… whether they are or anything else. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Good evening, gentlemen. It was fun.
Wade Brown: evening.
David Mendenhall: Alright, thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: Take care.